module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Adam has NEVER gone by which of the following names?', 
    a: 'Strawberry Rain',
    b: 'Dr. Helpin',
    c: 'Sparkles',
    d: 'Billy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Adrienne was known as all of these except:', 
    a: 'Joey',
    b: 'Slowwie',
    c: 'CanIndian',
    d: 'Rambo',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Autumn has also been known as:', 
    a: 'Apple Pie',
    b: 'Lil Tran',
    c: 'Apes',
    d: 'Penny',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'This person might respond to the nickname "The Mistake"', 
    a: 'Libby',
    b: 'JoCo',
    c: 'Couv',
    d: 'Mercan',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'ChelsBâ€™s (other) nickname is:', 
    a: 'Chelsyonnce',
    b: 'Cheesy',
    c: 'Chelsney',
    d: 'Cheech',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Kevin was once known as:', 
    a: 'The Big League Chew',
    b: 'Doc Oc(topus)',
    c: 'Magic Mustache',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who goes by the title "Rainy Day"?', 
    a: 'Darice',
    b: 'Glynn',
    c: 'Jessica',
    d: 'Marion',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which individual goes by the name "Eurotrash"?', 
    a: 'Mark P',
    b: 'Billy',
    c: 'Marcus',
    d: 'Tyler N',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Sean\'s nickname?', 
    a: 'Flea',
    b: 'Black Ice',
    c: 'The Situation',
    d: 'FatBoy Slim',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Joe\'s nickname?', 
    a: 'Viewtiful Joe',
    b: 'Mighty Joe Old',
    c: 'Bum',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];